<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="walkthrough_title_investigation">Investigation Screen</string>
    <string name="walkthrough_desc_investigation_1">Welcome to the Investigation screen! This is your main dashboard for tracking evidence and identifying the ghost.</string>

    <string name="walkthrough_title_journal">The Journal</string>
    <string name="walkthrough_desc_journal_1">The Journal is where you record evidence found during the investigation.</string>
    <string name="walkthrough_desc_journal_2">Select evidence to filter the list of possible ghosts. You can also tap on ghost names to see more details.</string>

    <string name="walkthrough_title_status">Status Bar</string>
    <string name="walkthrough_desc_status_1">Keep an eye on the status bar for your current sanity, the remaining preparation time, and the current weather.</string>

    <string name="walkthrough_title_toolbar">Tools &amp; Configs</string>
    <string name="walkthrough_desc_toolbar_1">The toolbar gives you access to various tools like the BPM counter, Timers, and Operation Configurations.</string>

    <string name="walkthrough_title_configs">Investigation Setup</string>
    <string name="walkthrough_desc_configs_1">Configure the map, difficulty, and weather for your investigation here. These settings affect the ghost\'s behavior and your rewards.</string>
    <string name="walkthrough_subtitle_configs_map">Map Selection</string>
    <string name="walkthrough_desc_configs_map">Select the location for your next investigation. Larger maps offer higher rewards but are more dangerous.</string>
    <string name="walkthrough_subtitle_configs_difficulty">Difficulty Settings</string>
    <string name="walkthrough_desc_configs_difficulty">Choose how challenging the investigation will be. Higher difficulties increase ghost aggression and multiplier.</string>
    <string name="walkthrough_subtitle_configs_weather">Weather Control</string>
    <string name="walkthrough_desc_configs_weather">Check or select the weather conditions. Weather affects visibility and can impact certain ghost behaviors.</string>
    <string name="walkthrough_subtitle_configs_temperature">Temperature Meter</string>
    <string name="walkthrough_desc_configs_temperature">Monitor the ambient temperature. Freezing temperatures are a key piece of evidence.</string>
    <string name="walkthrough_subtitle_configs_timer">Preparation Timer</string>
    <string name="walkthrough_desc_configs_timer">Track the remaining preparation time. Once it hits zero, the ghost can start hunting!</string>
    <string name="walkthrough_subtitle_configs_power">Fuse Box Button</string>
    <string name="walkthrough_desc_configs_power">Control the building\'s main fuse box. Keep the lights on to preserve your sanity!</string>
    <string name="walkthrough_subtitle_configs_death">Teammate Death</string>
    <string name="walkthrough_desc_configs_death">Record a teammate\'s unfortunate passing to adjust your investigation strategy.</string>
    <string name="walkthrough_subtitle_configs_medication">Sanity Medication</string>
    <string name="walkthrough_desc_configs_medication">Use sanity pills to restore your mental state and delay the onset of ghost hunts.</string>

    <string name="walkthrough_subtitle_configs_sanity">Sanity Meter</string>
    <string name="walkthrough_subtitle_configs_status">Status Bar</string>

    <string name="walkthrough_title_sanity">Sanity Management</string>
    <string name="walkthrough_desc_sanity_1">Your sanity drops over time in the dark. Use sanity pills to restore it, and be careful – low sanity makes you a target!</string>

    <string name="walkthrough_title_traits">Secondary Evidence</string>
    <string name="walkthrough_desc_traits_1">Identify secondary evidence traits to narrow down the ghost type. Some traits are unique to specific ghosts.</string>
    <string name="walkthrough_subtitle_traits_unique">Unique Traits Only</string>
    <string name="walkthrough_desc_traits_unique">Filter the list to only show traits that are unique to a single ghost. This is often the fastest way to confirm a specific identity.</string>
    <string name="walkthrough_subtitle_traits_filter">Category Filter</string>
    <string name="walkthrough_desc_traits_filter">Narrow down the list by selecting a specific category, such as "Behavior" or "Abilities", to find relevant evidence faster.</string>

    <string name="walkthrough_title_analyzer">Operation Details</string>
    <string name="walkthrough_desc_analyzer_1">Review the specific details of your current operation, including ghost behavior and investigation settings.</string>

    <string name="walkthrough_title_timers">Investigation Timers</string>
    <string name="walkthrough_desc_timers_1">Use these timers to track smudge stick effectiveness, hunt durations, and fingerprint persistence.</string>
    <string name="walkthrough_subtitle_timers_smudge">Smudge Stick Timer</string>
    <string name="walkthrough_desc_timers_smudge">Track how long a smudge stick prevents the ghost from hunting. Different ghosts have different prevention durations.</string>
    <string name="walkthrough_subtitle_timers_hunt_duration">Hunt Duration</string>
    <string name="walkthrough_desc_timers_hunt_duration">Monitor the length of an active hunt. This helps you know when it\'s safe to come out of hiding.</string>
    <string name="walkthrough_subtitle_timers_hunt_cooldown">Hunt Cooldown</string>
    <string name="walkthrough_desc_timers_hunt_cooldown">Track the minimum time between hunts. Use this window to move between hiding spots or gather evidence.</string>
    <string name="walkthrough_subtitle_timers_link">Linked Timers</string>
    <string name="walkthrough_desc_timers_link">When linked, the cooldown timer starts automatically as soon as the hunt duration timer finishes, providing a seamless timeline.</string>
    <string name="walkthrough_subtitle_timers_fingerprint">Fingerprint Timer</string>
    <string name="walkthrough_desc_timers_fingerprint">Track how long fingerprints will remain visible. This helps you know if you need to re-check a door or window.</string>

    <string name="walkthrough_title_footstep">Footstep Analyzer</string>
    <string name="walkthrough_desc_footstep_1">Measure the ghost\'s movement speed (BPM) to help identify it. Different ghosts have distinct walking speeds.</string>
    <string name="walkthrough_subtitle_footstep_modifiers">Active Modifiers</string>
    <string name="walkthrough_desc_footstep_modifiers">See how the current investigation settings, such as weather or ghost speed modifiers, are affecting the ghost\'s movement.</string>
    <string name="walkthrough_subtitle_footstep_apply">Apply Measurement</string>
    <string name="walkthrough_desc_footstep_apply">Choose which measurement (Instant, Average, or Weighted) to apply to your investigation to help narrow down the ghost type.</string>
    <string name="walkthrough_subtitle_footstep_visualizer">BPM Visualizer</string>
    <string name="walkthrough_desc_footstep_visualizer">Tap along with the ghost\'s footsteps to see its movement speed graphed in real-time. Use the dropdowns to adjust the view.</string>
</resources>
